hoopladigital.com 2015-03-18

# hoopla

## Privacy Policy

**Midwest Tape, LLC** and its affiliates (Midwest Tape, CVS Midwest, hoopla) provides digital content, software applications, technology services, and hosted websites for third parties. This privacy policy applies to all Midwest Tape hosted websites, applications and services (www.hoopladigital.com and its related services; collectively the "Services") 

Midwest Tape is committed to protecting the privacy, accuracy, and reliability of any personal information provided and to safeguard loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, and alteration of this information. This privacy policy sets out to make you aware of how hoopla uses and/or shares any information that is gathered in the use of this website or app. 

The hoopla app offers a wide variety of content. However, not all our sources may be relied upon to provide accurate, complete or current information. Some of the information may even be viewed as offensive, inaccurate, or controversial. Library Systems, library users, and any other third party users are responsible for their own use of the app and parents are responsible for their children's use of the Internet. 

Midwest Tape evaluates ongoing our Privacy Policy against new technologies, business practices, and our users' needs, and may make changes to the Privacy Policy accordingly. Please check this page periodically for updates. Your continued use of the Service after posting of any changes to this Privacy Policy means that you agree to be bound by such changes. 

### What is "personal information"?

"Personal Information" describes information that can be associated with a specific user and used to identify that person, such as name, email address, birthday, gender, location information, etc. You may submit Personal Information when you use the hoopla Services. Other information, not personally identifiable, may be collected automatically when visiting or using the Services. The app works in conjunction with your library system so your library card number is necessary (optional is the library card PIN) to verify that you are a patron in good standing with the library. An email address and password, submitted by you, will be used to authenticate you when you use the hoopla service. 

The hoopla service records how you use our application, including by not limited to; online activity, digital content selections, reviews and ratings, and operating systems. Personal Information remains anonymous. This information is reported in aggregate (no personal identifier) to your library, content providers, and licensing agencies. 

### What do we use your information for?

  * We use your email address and password to authenticate you with our systems.
  * We use your library card number and library card PIN to authenticate you with your library's systems.
  * We use a record of the materials you borrow to bill your library for usage and to pay license fees.
  * We use usage data to look for ways to improve the hoopla service, by making popular features easier to find, getting rid of features that few people use, or anticipating features people may wish we had.
  * We may use your email in response to a specific inquiry or complaint you may have posted to us.
  * We may use your email address to send information about the hoopla service, such as; updates to the service, new major features and/or content information, unless you have opt out of receiving the information.
  * In all circumstances, your information -- whether public or private -- will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, other than for the express purpose of being able to deliver the product or service.

### How do we protect your information?

Your privacy is important to us. We have implemented measures to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of your Personal Information. All electronic communication between your web browser or mobile device and our servers is protected and encrypted via SSL (HTTPS). Your password is encrypted before it is stored in our database. We use computer safeguards such as firewalls and data encryption and physical access controls to our buildings and files. Midwest Tape uses commercially reasonable efforts to comply with this Privacy Policy but cannot guarantee error-free performance under this Policy. Midwest Tape will take prompt corrective action if it learns of any failure to comply with the Privacy Policy. Midwest Tape will not be liable for any incidental, indirect, consequential or punitive damages or for loss of profit or opportunity, loss of use or other financial loss arising out of or relating to this Privacy Policy. 

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to third parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party links on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

### What if I share information with others while using the hoopla service?

While using the hoopla service, you may have opportunities to post reviews, rate digital content, and share digital content information with others in public forums and on social networking websites such as Facebook, and Twitter. When you share this information, it is made public but not subject to this Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for any third party's use of information you publicly display or disclose through our Service. 

### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and mobile applications, and not to information collected offline. 

### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at https://www.hoopladigital.com/terms. 

### You're Consenting

By using our site or mobile applications, you're consenting to our online privacy policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this policy, you can email them to [info@hoopladigital.com](mailto:info@hoopladigital.com) and we'll respond accordingly.

These Terms are effective as of June 2014
